The polarity field brings about the notochordal process.
極性場は脊索形成過程を導きます。
This notochordal process influences the neuronal system.
この脊索形成過程は神経系に影響を与えます。
This neuronal system will influence the cardiac system,
この神経系は心臓系に影響を与え、
which itself, in a way, leads to the establishment at the diaphragmatic level,
それ自体がある意味で横隔膜レベルでの形成を導き、
at the level of the septum transversum, thus the diaphragmatization,
横中隔の平面上で、すなわち横隔膜形成です。
which leads to the development of my adrenal glands.
それが副腎の発達を引き起こします。
This is a movement that happens here, and then here there is the
これはここで行われる動きであり、そしてここにあります。
future development for my
私の将来の発達のための
adrenal glands, okay, by the growth of the liver here, it will create a suction field here, I
副腎、よろしいですか。肝臓の成長によって、ここで吸引場が形成されます。ここで私は
have the liver.
肝臓を持っています。
And it will create a posterior space here in the posterior parietal peritoneum, and it's by
そしてそれがここで後方壁側腹膜内に後方の空間を形成します。そしてそれは
this
〜によってです。
growth that you will see at the posterior part here, like a suction field that
この成長によって、ここの後方部分レベルで吸引場のようなものが見られるでしょう。それが
will give these adrenal glands that become very, very large, they are there because they
その副腎を与え、それが非常に大きくなります。そこにあるのは、それが
They also have this genetic information in the tissue.
それらは組織内にもこの遺伝情報を持っています。
Initially, the urogenital system means that there are cells
まず最初に、泌尿生殖器系は細胞が存在するようにします。
that are around my vitelline vesicle here.
ここで私の卵黄嚢の周囲にある細胞です。
You see, that is, there is a migration of gonocytes coming from the vitelline vesicle
ご覧の通り、すなわち卵黄嚢から来る生殖細胞の移動があります。
and which come to this part to colonize what we call
そしてこの部分に来て、私たちが呼ぶものを定着させます。
the genital ridge.
生殖腺稜です。
At the posterior wall, these small gonocytes come to swell this epithelium.
後壁レベルで、これらの小さな生殖細胞がこの上皮を膨張させに来ます。
They inform this epithelium by a suction field, and this epithelium
吸引場によってこの上皮に情報をもたらし、そしてこの上皮は
that was there, all of a sudden begins to thicken and form a gonadal ridge.
そこにあったものが、突然厚くなり始め、生殖腺稜を形成します。
But above, on the side, I have, through the liver and through this development, my adrenal glands that grow and
しかしその上では、側方では、肝臓とこの発達によって私の副腎が成長し、
which push my gonads to the side.
私の生殖腺を側方へ押し出します。
These are the gonads, these are my adrenal glands, on both sides, left and right.
これが生殖腺、これが私の副腎で、左右両側にあります。
By this movement of your mind, it comes to push.
あなたの精神のこの動きによって、それが押し出されます。
Here, it will create a lateral fold by the movement of
ここで、〜の動きによって側方のひだが形成されます。
my adrenal glands pushing the gonads.
私の副腎が生殖腺を押し出す動きです。
It will create a fold in the tissue, because it does like this.
それが組織内にひだを形成します。なぜならそれがこのように作用するからです。
Adrenal glands, kidneys, those, this is the ovarian zone, it's the genital ridge,
副腎、腎臓、それらが卵巣領域、すなわち生殖堤です。
you see here.
ここに見えますね。
Initially, this line here represents what we call the Müllerian
最初は、ここのこの線はいわゆる
duct.
ミュラー管を表しています。
A kind of fold like that, in the parietal peritoneum.
壁側腹膜に、このようなひだがあります。
posterior. A fold on the left and on the right. At this stage, there is no
後方に、左右にひだがあります。この段階では、まだ
difference
違いは
yet between male and female. In females, on a structural level,
男性と女性の間にありません。女性では、構造的に、
it's already
すでに
done at the genetic level, the adrenal glands are more important, more developed
遺伝子レベルで決定されており、副腎はより大きく、より発達しています。
and therefore push the lateral movement more strongly. We
そのため、側方への動きをより強く押し出します。我々は
see a fold appearing in the tissue here
ここに組織内にひだが現れるのが見えます。
by this movement. And this kind of fold here,
この動きによって。そして、ここのこのひだは、
laterally, it will give the fallopian tubes
側方に、卵管を形成します。
on the left and on the right
左右に、
but in the middle here
しかし、ここの中央では、
I have the reunion
結合が見られます。
by my liver which is now pulling in this tilt
私の肝臓が今、この傾きの中で引っ張ることによって、
and bringing everything together like this
そして、すべてをこのように引き寄せます。
and at the same time, I will have
そして同時に、
my lower limbs
私の下肢が
that start to come out here
ここから出始め、
and so it creates a line here
そして、ここに線が形成されます。
and a movement on the median line
そして正中線上の動きが
you see these two tubes here, come together like this
ここのこれら二つの管が、このように結合するのが見えますね。
you see
見えますね。
and the reunion of the two
そして、この二つの結合が、
by the liver, organized by the liver above, which energizes
上方にある肝臓によって組織され、肝臓によって活性化され、
the adrenal glands, which pushes more
副腎を、より強く押し出し、
strongly my lateral gonads, and by this movement, creates this line here. But
私の側方の生殖腺を、そしてこの動きによって、ここにこの線を形成します。しかし、
above, the liver
上方に、肝臓が
comes back to pull with the opening of the same here above, and the reunion of the two, of the
同じく上方に開口部を伴って引き戻され、そして二つの、
two
二つの
tubes here, will form the uterus. In men, the difference is that this canal, it
ここにある管が子宮を形成します。男性の場合、この管は
regresses,
退縮しますが、
but in fact, it doesn't go that far.
しかし実際には、そこまで発達しません。
It doesn't happen.
それは形成されません。
You see, in women, it closes.
女性ではそれが閉鎖します。
And what does that give?
そしてそれは、何をもたらしますか？
It gives the fallopian tube.
それは卵管になります。
And here, you will have the gonad developing,
そしてここでは、生殖腺が発達します。
which will later become the ovary and will make its space through here, you see, and through here.
それが後に卵巣となり、ここやここからその空間を形成します。
The uterus is made of posterior parietal peritoneum.
子宮は、後壁側腹膜由来です。
All of this, what is it?
これら全ては、何ですか？
It's my broad ligament.
それは広靭帯です。
With lines inside here which will be the ovarian ligament
ここにある内部の線は、卵巣靭帯となるでしょう。
or the uterosacral ligament.
あるいは仙骨子宮靭帯です。
or the broad ligament, but in fact, it's all posterior parietal peritoneum.
あるいは広靭帯ですが、実際には、それは全て後壁側腹膜です。
So, firstly, there is this migration.
したがって、まず、この移動があります。
I have the genital ridge that is informed, that develops.
生殖隆起が形成され、発達します。
This genital ridge, with the adrenal glands here just before,
この生殖隆起は、その直前にある腎臓の構造物と共に、
is connected to the development of the liver.
肝臓の発達と関連しています。
The development of the liver creates a new retroperitoneal space.
肝臓の発達は、新たな後腹膜腔を形成します。
This suction field, because it's a gland, so it's a tissue.
この吸引領域は、それが腺であるため、組織です。
which is aspirated, as we had seen for all glands.
全ての腺で見たように、吸引されます。
It comes to push my gonads, the kidneys, it will make the mesonephros disappear.
それは生殖腺、腎臓を押し、中腎を消失させます。
However, my gonadal ridge pushes more and more laterally,
しかし、生殖腺隆起はますます外側へと成長し、
and the system does this, and creates a fold in the posterior parietal peritoneum.
そしてシステムはこれを行い、後壁側腹膜にひだを形成します。
And this tube will be called the Müllerian tubercle.
そしてこの管は、ミュラー管と呼ばれるでしょう。
While the first level that came from this collecting tube,
一方、この集合管に由来する最初の段階は、
which we call the mesonephric duct,
中腎管と呼ばれるもの、
it's called the Wolffian duct. That one is already there. It
ウォルフ管と呼ばれます。それは既に存在し、
will serve as a conduit later for my gonadal ridge,
後に生殖腺稜の導管として機能し、
so future testicle or future ovaries, with the diaphragmatic suspensory ligament
すなわち将来の精巣または卵巣、横隔膜懸垂靭帯とともに、
and below the gubernaculum
そして下方には導帯が
which will guide to bring the ovaries back into
卵巣をその位置へと導き、
their place according to this,
これに基づいて、
or in men, bring it back to the inguinal canal and the patients.
あるいは男性では、精巣を鼠径管のレベルまで誘導し、
in the pants.
陰嚢内へと導きます。